// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How can you add Page Number?",
    answer: "D. Click Insert > Header & Footer > Page Number > Choose Format > Choose Style",
    options: [
      "A. Click Insert > Header > choose style",
      "B. Click Insert > Footer > Choose Format > Choose Style",
      "C. Click Insert > Header & Footer > Page Number > Choose Style",
      "D. Click Insert > Header & Footer > Page Number > Choose Format > Choose Style"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "It is a computer program or device that provides for input, editing, formatting and output of text, often with some additional features.",
    answer: "D. Word",
    options: [
      "A. Outlook",
      "B. Presentation",
      "C. Spreadsheet",
      "D. Word"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How will you edit the page number in the Table of Contents?",
    answer: "C. Highlight the desired page number and edit it",
    options: [
      "A. Ctrl + a then delete",
      "B. Highlight the desired page number and delete",
      "C. Highlight the desired page number and edit it",
      "D. Click the page number and erase before you edit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the first step in adding footer?",
    answer: "A. Click Insert",
    options: [
      "A. Click Insert",
      "B. Click Home",
      "C. Press Ctrl + H",
      "D. Click References"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Word processor is best described as _______.",
    answer: "C. Document software",
    options: [
      "A. Outlook",
      "B. Database software",
      "C. Document software",
      "D. Presentation software"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "When should Heading Styles be applied in the Table of Contents procedure?",
    answer: "B. Type the text then apply Heading Styles “while” creating the Table of Contents",
    options: [
      "A. Type the text then apply Heading Styles “after” creating the Table of Contents",
      "B. Type the text then apply Heading Styles “while” creating the Table of Contents",
      "C. Type the text then apply Heading Styles “before” creating the Table of Contents",
      "D. Type the text then apply Heading Style  “during” creating the Table of Contents"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In what part of tab ribbon, you can change the font style of the text?",
    answer: "B. Home",
    options: [
      "A. Design",
      "B. Home",
      "C. Layout",
      "D. View"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Why are page numbers required in a Table of Contents?",
    answer: "C. To help readers find in which page the topic can be located.",
    options: [
      "A. To have more pages to read.",
      "B. To make the work more appealing.",
      "C. To help readers find in which page the topic can be located.",
      "D. To help and simply scan for a topic by pressing Ctrl+F function."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which ribbon includes Header and Footer?",
    answer: "D. Insert ribbon, Header & Footer",
    options: [
      "A. Home ribbon, Font",
      "B. Insert ribbon, Paragraph",
      "C. Home ribbon, Header & Footer",
      "D. Insert ribbon, Header & Footer"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Dave wants to change the style of the header in his document. Which ribbon he needs to click that contains styles?",
    answer: "A. Design",
    options: [
      "A. Design",
      "B. Home",
      "C. Insert",
      "D. Layout"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What common type of application software does the Microsoft Word belong?",
    answer: "D. Word Processing",
    options: [
      "A. Presentation",
      "B. Spreadsheet",
      "C. Text-editor",
      "D. Word Processing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Jane is inserting page numbers in her research project document. Which of the following is NOT a process of inserting an automatic page number in her document?",
    answer: "A. Click the Insert ribbon and press enter.",
    options: [
      "A. Click the Insert ribbon and press enter.",
      "B. Copy a document from another file that has a page number.",
      "C. Click the Insert ribbon, search for the Header & Footer group and click page number.",
      "D. Double click the footer section of a page in the document, click on the page number in Header & Footer group and select the page number"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which ribbon opens headers and footers?",
    answer: "B. Insert",
    options: [
      "A. Home",
      "B. Insert",
      "C. References",
      "D. View"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Aira needs to apply a formatting element in the page number of her document. Which of the following options does NOT describe as a formatting element?",
    answer: "D. Text alignment and Page number",
    options: [
      "A. Text Alignment",
      "B. Bold, italic and underline",
      "C. Font, Font size and font color",
      "D. Text alignment and Page number"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The upper part of the document is known as _______.",
    answer: "B. Header",
    options: [
      "A. Footer Header",
      "B. Header",
      "C. Margin",
      "D. Top Reference"
    ]
  },
];
